Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 3, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: The Hired Farm Working Force of 1967; a Statistical Report, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Notes: September 1968
  - Item 3: Hired Farmworkers in the United States, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Hired Farm Workers in the United States, 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Family and Hired Labor Used on U.S. Farms in 1966, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Summary of Rules, Regulations and Laws that Affect Seasonal Farm and Food Processing Workers and their Employers in New York State, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: New York State
    Notes: July 1963
- Box: 3, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for the Seasonal Industry Determination for the Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Industry Under the Fair Labor Standards Act May 1972, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Rural Manpower Center, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: Lauren H. Brown
    Notes: May 1967
  - Item 3: Migratory Farmworkers in the Midcontinent Streams, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: United States Department of Agriculture
  - Item 4: Labor Used on Farms, 1964 and 1966, 1970; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: October 1970
  - Item 5: The Tenure Status of Farmworkers in the United States, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 1960
  - Item 6: The Hired Farm Working Force of 1971: A Statistical Report, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: March 1972
  - Item 7: A Socio-Economic Profile of the 1965 Farm Wage Force, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Notes: April 1969
- Box: 3, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Farm Labor in the United States, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Author: University of Illinois
    Notes: April 1971
  - Item 2: Guide to Sources on Agricultural Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Author: Isao Fumimoto & Jo Clare Schieffer
- Box: 3, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Status of Agricultural Workers Under State and Federal Labor Laws, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: The Farm Labor Situation in Selected States, 1965-66, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Box: 3, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Farm Labor Situation in Washington, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Author: Washington Agricultural Experiment Station
    Notes: September 1971
- Box: 3, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Report to the National Labor Board by Special Commission, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb 11, 1934
- Box: 3, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Farm and Machinery, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Author: George E. Sokolsky
    Notes: June 1940
- Box: 3, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Farm Wage Boards, 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: University of California, Berkeley
    Notes: June 2, 1941
- Box: 3, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: How Farm People Learn New Methods, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Author: Lauren Soth
    Notes: October 1952
- Box: 3, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Manpower Outlook '80, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Author: Arizona State Employment Service
    Notes: November 1968
- Box: 3, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Occupational Disease in California Attributed to Pesticides and Other Agricultural Chemicals, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Box: 3, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Underemployment in American Agriculture, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Author: Arthur Moore
    Notes: January 1952
- Box: 3, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: People With Farm Earnings, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Box: 3, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: The Agrarian Reform Law of the People's Republic of China, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Author: Foreign Languages Press
- Box: 3, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Aerospace Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Author: Department of Industrial Relations
    Notes: January 1967
- Box: 3, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Personnel Department Pay Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Author: State of Alabama
    Notes: October 16, 1968
- Box: 3, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Current Population Estimates, 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Author: Alaska Department of Labor
    Notes: July 1, 1965
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: What Employers are Doing About Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Management Information Center, Inc.
  - Item 2: Quarterly Journal of Studies on Alcohol: Supplement Number 3, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Rutgers University
    Notes: April 1965
  - Item 3: Report by the Scientific Advisory Council on the Alcoholism Research Grant Program, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Liscensed Beverage Industries, Inc.
  - Item 4: Florida's Public Health Program on Alcoholism, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: State of Florida Alcoholic Rehabilitation Program
  - Item 5: Alcoholism and the Federal Employee, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: HSMHA Employee Health Program on Alcoholism, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Health Services and Mental Health Administration
    Notes: January 1973
  - Item 7: Guidelines to Organizing for Community Action, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: S. George Clarke
  - Item 8: The Key Step, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: United States Civil Service Commission
    Notes: January 1969
  - Item 9: The Rights of Alcoholics and Their Families, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: The New York City Affiliate, Inc.
  - Item 10: How to Recognize and HELP the Alcoholic on Your Payroll, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Darnell Office Administration
  - Item 11: You and the Drinking Driving Laws, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: New York State Department of Motor Vehicles
  - Item 12: Occupational Alcoholism: Some Problems and Some Solutions, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism
  - Item 13: Alcohol and Accidental Injury, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Alcoholism, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Problem Drinking in Industry: A Survey of the Syracuse Metropolitan Area, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Robert Raful
    Notes: August 1959
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Key Step, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Alcoholism Rehabilitation, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Cahiers Nord-Africains, Le Fonds d'Action Sociale, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: Bimestrielle
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Africains du Nord au Travail en France, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Immigration and Naturalization Service Urged to Exclude Alien Strikebreakers, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: American Council for Nationalities Service
    Notes: October 10, 1967
  - Item 2: Die Beschaftigung Auslandischer Arbeitskrafte in der Schweiz, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Bank Hofmann
  - Item 3: The Immigration Bill & The Industrial Relations Bill, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Barrie Sherman
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Aluminum: The Industry and the Four North American Producers, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Author: First Boston Corporation
- Box: 4, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ILPA Local Publications Guide, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Author: International Labor Press Association
  - Item 2: ILPA Press Relations Guide, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box: 4, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Whittier and the Amesbury-Salisbury Strike, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: Thomas Franklin Currier
- Box: 4, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of the Joint Legislative Committee on Winter Tourist Business, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Author: State of New York
- Box: 4, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: How to Find U.S. Statutes and U.S. Code Citations, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Author: Committee on the Judiciary
- Box: 4, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Investigation of the Effectiveness of Antiracketeering Laws and the Administration Thereof, 1947; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Author: Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments
    Notes: April 7, 1947
- Box: 4, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Communist Anti-Semitism, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Author: Elizabeth M. Thompson
    Notes: Jan 5, 1953
- Box: 4, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Facing a Union Drive, 1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Author: Research Institute of America
- Box: 4, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Profile of the Appalachian Family, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Author: Jack E. Weller
    Notes: June 1968
- Box: 4, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employment, Unemployment, and Low Incomes in Appalachia, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Notes: May 1965
- Box: 4, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: It's Your Job!, 1947; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: John W. Teele
  - Item 2: Job Letters, 1942; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: A.A. Liveright
  - Item 3: How to Land the Position You Want, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: Matilda Rogers
  - Item 4: Your Job Letter, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Job Finder; It Pays to Advertise, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: S. Norman Feingold
  - Item 6: Your New Career; Planning for Retirement, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: Departmant of the Navy
  - Item 7: Merchandising Your Job Talents, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Guide to Preparing a Resume, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: How to Get and Hold the Right Job, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: How to Get the Job You Want After 40, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: Maxwell J. Harper and Arthur R. Pell
  - Item 11: What Employers Want, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: James C. Worthy
- Box: 4, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship in Modern Education, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Author: Wayne University
- Box: 4, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Standards of Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Is Apprenticeship Outdated?, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Author: EJ Singer and ID Macdonald
  - Item 3: Apprenticeship Past and Present, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Community Apprenticeship Program; A Feasibility Program, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Author: Thomas S. Isaack
- Box: 4, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship: Chapter 187 of the Laws; 1964 Edition, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Author: The Government Printer
    Notes: Northern Rhodesia
- Box: 4, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship in New South Wales in 1962, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Author: N.S.W. Industrial Gazette
    Notes: January 1963
- Box: 4, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Automobile Mechanic, Body Repairman and Painter, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Box: 4, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Standards of Apprenticeship for Auto Mechanics, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Automobile Mechanic, Body Repairman and Painter, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Box: 4, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Associated Retail Bakers of America National Apprenticeship and Training Policy, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Associated Retail Bakers of America, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Box: 4, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: National Bricklaying Apprenticeship Program and Standards, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Box: 4, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship Standards for Operating Engineers, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Box: 4, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Building Apprenticeship and Training Council: Third Report, 1947; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Author: Ministry of Works
    Notes: December 1946
- Box: 4, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Apprenticeship Law in California, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Author: California Department of Industrial Relations
  - Item 2: The California Plan for Equal Opportunity, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Tips on How to Become a Skilled Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: March 1963
  - Item 4: Craftsmanship Through Apprenticeship, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: June 1957
- Box: 4, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship in Canada, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: King's Printer and Controller of Stationery
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship in Manufacturing, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Department of Labour
  - Item 3: An Act to Amend the Apprenticeship and Tradesmen's Qualification Act, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: L.R. Peterson
  - Item 4: Technical and Vocational Training Branch: Number of Registered Apprentices by Occupation, by Province, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Notes: April 1, 1965
  - Item 5: Registered Apprenticeship Training, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Department of Citizenship and Immigration
  - Item 6: An Act to Amend the Apprenticeship Act, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Frank Fogg, Queen's Printer
    Notes: 1962-63
  - Item 7: The Apprenticeship and Tradesmen's Qualification Act, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Box: 4, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and Training in Carpentry Construction, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Carpentry, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Carpentry, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Setting Up an Apprenticeship Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Employment of Apprentices, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: January 8, 1973
- Box: 4, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Draftsmen, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Box: 4, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: National Standards for Carpentry Apprenticeship, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: National Standards of Apprenticeship for the Crafts of the Plastering Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: National Roofers Apprenticeship and Training Standards, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: National Bricklaying Apprenticeship Program and Standards, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Box: 4, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship in Denmark, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Author: Ireland National Apprenticeship Board
- Box: 4, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and Training Policy for Dental Laboratory Technicians, Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Dental Technicians, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Box: 4, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for the Electrical Industry, 1945; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Author: War Manpower Commission
- Box: 4, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The TVA Apprenticeship Program, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Author: Tennessee Valley Authority
    Notes: July 1968
  - Item 2: Una Revolucion Pacifica, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Author: Rodolfo Martinez Tono
  - Item 3: La Formation Professionelle, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Author: Valentin F. Cuervas
- Box: 4, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training and the Agencies Involved for Hesse, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Author: Howard B Gundersen
    Notes: 19 September 1949
- Box: 4, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Apprentices Act, 1961, Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Author: Government Printer
- Box: 4, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for the Stained Glass Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for Glaziers and Glassworkers, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Box: 4, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Craft Apprenticeship; Training for a Skilled Craft or Trade, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Author: The Industrial Training Council
    Notes: August 1962
  - Item 2: Craft Apprenticeship, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Author: British Steel Corporation
  - Item 3: Apprentice Training for the Sixties, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Author: Industrial Welfare Society
  - Item 4: Building Apprenticeship: Recruitment and Training, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Notes: November 1948
- Box: 4, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Act, 1959, Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Author: The Stationery Office
    Language: Gaelic; English.
- Box: 4, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and Training Policy for Cash Register Repairmen, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Box: 4, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship Standards for the Retail Meat Cutting Industry, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Box: 4, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for the Sheet Metal Industry, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Box: 4, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for the Sheet Metal Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Box: 4, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Report of the Nebraska Legislative Council Sub-Committee on Apprenticeship Councils, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Author: Nebraska Legislative Council
  - Item 2: The Apprenticeship Act, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Author: Baptist Johnson
  - Item 3: Apprenticeship in the Netherlands, Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Author: Irish Printers Limited
- Box: 4, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Some Dimensions of the Drop-Out Problem in Apprenticeship Training, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Author: New Brunswick Department of Labour
    Notes: March 1967
  - Item 2: A Second Look at the Drop-Out Problem in Apprenticeship Training, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Box: 4, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Report on a Study to Determine the Trades in Which Apprentices are Employed and the Number of Employed Apprentices Enrolled in Related Instruction Classes, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Author: State of New Jersey Department of Education
    Notes: March 1964
- Box: 4, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship in New South Wales, 1962-1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Author: Industrial Gazette
- Box: 4, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training Regulations, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Author: State of New York Department of Labor
    Notes: September 1, 1964
  - Item 2: The Extent of Registered Apprentice Training in New York State, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Item 3: Protect Your Future Through Apprentice Training: An Investment with Dividends, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Box: 4, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship in Norway, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Training in Nova Scotia, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Nova Scotia Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Provincial Conference on Apprenticeship, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 27 & 28, 1964
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: National Painting and Decorating Apprenticeship and Training Standards, 1967; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Box: 5, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for the Graphic Arts International Union, 1975; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: General Apprenticeship Standards for Graphic Arts Industry in Buffalo, New York, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Allied Printing Trades Unions of Buffalo, New York
- Box: 5, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Apprenticeship Act of 1964, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: S.G. Reid, Government Printer
- Box: 5, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: National Roofers Apprenticeship and Training Standards, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Box: 5, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: National Trucking Industry Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship and Training Standards, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training for Job Skill, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: Bureau of Reclamation
  - Item 2: Reports on Apprentice Selection Programs (3), 1950; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Notes: June 1950
  - Item 3: Reports on Apprentice Selection Programs (1), Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Reports on Apprentice Selection Programs (2), 1950; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Notes: May 1950
  - Item 5: The National Apprenticeship Program, 1949; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The National Apprenticeship Program, 1947; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Apprenticeship Credit for Previous Experience, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Report on Apprentice Training Program of the Tennessee Valley Authority, 1947; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Notes: July 1947
  - Item 9: Occupation Statistics of Registered Apprentices, 1949; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Notes: April 1949
  - Item 10: Report of Conference of State Apprenticeship Agencies, 1946; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Notes: March 25-28, 1946
- Box: 5, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and Economic Change, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)